Hubbell Trading Post records, 1882-1968 (bulk 1905-1950)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Sub-group III: Business Books and Records, 1882-1967
  - Series I: Daily Records, 1882-1967
    - Pinon: daybook, cashbook, pawn, shipments. 1921-1922 (Box 462, Folder 1)
    - Pinon: various accounts. 1924 (Box 462, Folder 3)
    - Pinon: bank accounts, sheep and cattle. 1926 (Box 462, Folder 4)
    - Pinon: cattle. 1927, 1929 (Box 462, Folder 5)
    - Pinon: daily sheets, monthly sheets, yearly sheets. 1931-1946 (Box 462, Folder 6)
    - Pinon: rugs. 1933 (Box 462, Folder 7a-7b)
    - Pinon: rugs. 1933 (Box 463, Folder 1)
    - Pinon: Indian accounts, ledger sheets. 1952 (Box 463, Folder 2)
    - Pioneer Liquor Store: stock records, ledger sheets (parts 1-2); San Benito Ranch Store: various accounts, miscellaneous. 1889, 1935-1936 (Box 463, Folder 3-4)
    - Sheep Springs: cashbook, various accounts. 1915-1917 (Box 463, Folder 5)
    - Shonto (not known if this belonged to the Hubbells): daily sheets (p.3-178), sheep bought (p.180-189), dipping records (p.189-191), cattle bought (p.194-195). 1923-1925 (Box 463, Folder 6)
    - Tenebito: Indian and various accounts, cattle, pawn. 1923-1929 (Box 464, Folder 1)
    - Tenebito: cashbook, pawn, sales, credits, dipping records, accounts (Herman Peterson, Charles E. Rubi), Indian accounts. 1929-1933 (Box 464, Folder 2)
    - Tenebito: Indian accounts. 1929-1933 (Box 464, Folder 3)
    - Tenebito: cashbook, accounts, wool shipped, "sales 1931." 1930-1931 (Box 464, Folder 4a-4b)
    - Tenebito: various accounts, ledger sheets. 1939 (Box 464, Folder 5)
    - Tenebito: daily sheets, monthly summaries (part 1). January-February 1923, December 1929-April 1930 (Box 464, Folder 6)
    - Tenebito: daily sheets, monthly summaries (part 2). May-September 1930 (Box 464, Folder 7)
    - Tenebito: daily, weekly, monthly sheets, and weekly and yearly summaries (part 1). January 1931-January 1933 (Box 464, Folder 8)
    - Tenebito: daily, weekly, monthly sheets, and weekly and yearly summaries (part 2). February 1, 1933-December 1941 (Box 464, Folder 9)
    - Tenebito: daily sheets, monthly sheets (part 1). January-April 1943 (Box 465, Folder 1)
    - Tenebito: daily sheets, monthly sheets (part 2). May-August 1943 (Box 465, Folder 2)
    - Tenebito: daily sheets, monthly sheets (part 3). August 1943-August 1946 (Box 465, Folder 3)
    - Tenebito: Indian accounts, loose sheets. 1934, 1941-1942, 1945 (Box 465, Folder 4)
    - Tenebito: Indian and various accounts, sheep and goat skins. 1934 (Box 465, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: wool. 1935-1936 (Box 465, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: wool, pinons. 1937-1940 (Box 465, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: rugs. 1937 (Box 465, Folder 8)
    - Winslow: rugs. 1937-1938 (Box 465, Folder 9)
    - Winslow: rugs. 1938 (Box 465, Folder 10)
    - Winslow: general ledger sheets. 1941-1943 (Volume 466)
    - Winslow: daily entry sheets. March-November 1940 (Volume 467)
    - Winslow: cashbook. December 1939-November 1941 (Box 468, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: cashbook. December 1941-March 27, 1943 (Box 468, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: cashbook. April 1943-February 7, 1944 (Box 468, Folder 3)
    - Winslow: cashbook. February 8-July 29, 1944 (Box 468, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: cashbook. July 31, 1944-January 20, 1945 (Box 468, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: cashbook. January 22-September 6, 1945 (Volume 469)
    - Winslow: cashbook. September 7, 1945-May 3, 1946 (Box 470, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: cashbook. May 4-July 26, 1946 (Box 470, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: cashbook. July 27, 1946-March 3, 1947 (Box 470, Folder 3a-3b)
    - Winslow: general journal sheets. 1943 (Volume 471)
    - Winslow: general journal sheets. December 1944-November 1945 (Volume 472)
    - Winslow: general journal sheets. December 1946-March 1947 (Volume 473)
    - Winslow: cash journal sheets (part 1). December 3, 1945-May 31, 1946 (Box 474, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: cash journal sheets (part 2). June 1-October 31, 1946 (Box 474, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: various accounts, ledger sheets. (parts 1-4). 1941-1947 (Box 474, Folder 3-6)
    - Winslow: wool. 1940-1942 (Box 474, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: wool. 1941-1942 (Box 474, Folder 8)
    - Winslow: wool, skins, pinons, shipments (sent and received). 1943 (Box 474, Folder 9)
    - Winslow: wool shipped. 1944 (Box 474, Folder 10)
    - Winslow: various accounts, ledger sheets (parts 1-5). 1929-1940 (Box 475, Folder 1-5)
    - Winslow: various accounts, ledger sheets (parts6-7). 1929-1940 (Box 476, Folder 1-2)
    - Winslow: various accounts, ledger sheets (parts 1-3). 1936-1941 (Box 476, Folder 3-5)
    - Winslow: various accounts, ledger sheets. 1941-1946 (Volume 477)
    - Winslow: various accounts, ledger sheets. 1944-1951 (Volume 478)
    - Winslow: various accounts, ledger sheets. 1945-1946 (Volume 479)
    - Winslow: various accounts, other posts, ledger sheets. December 1945-August 1946 (Volume 480)
    - Winslow: various accounts, other posts, ledger sheets. December 1946-October 1948 (Volume 481)
    - Winslow: accounts, other posts, ledger sheets (parts 1-6). 1941-1948 (Box 482, Folder 1-6)
    - Winslow: rugs. 1942 (Box 482, Folder 7)
    - Winslow: rugs. 1943 (Box 482, Folder 8a-8b)
    - Winslow: rugs. 1943-1944 (Box 482, Folder 9)
    - Winslow: rugs. 1945 (Box 483, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: rugs. 1946 (Box 483, Folder 2)
    - Winslow: rugs. 1947-1952 (Box 483, Folder 3)
    - Winslow: rugs. 1948-1951 (Box 483, Folder 4)
    - Winslow: pawn. 1944-1945 (Box 483, Folder 5)
    - Winslow: pawn. 1948 (Box 483, Folder 6)
    - Winslow: cash receipts, disbursements, purchase journal, general journal. September1943-November 1944 (Volume 484)
    - Winslow: assets and liabilities, profits and loans, journal sheets. 1947-1952 (Volume 485)
    - Winslow: cash disbursements and receipts (part 1). March 1947-December 1948 (Volume 486)
    - Winslow: cash disbursements and receipts (part 2). 1948-1950 (Volume 487)
    - Winslow: cash disbursements and receipts (part 3). January 1951-June 26, 1952 (Volume 488)
    - Winslow: cash receipts and disbursements. 1948-1952 (Volume 489)
    - Winslow: general journal. December 6, 1948-January 1951 (Volume 490)
    - Winslow: pawn. 1948 (Box 491, Folder 1)
    - Winslow: pawn (inventories). 1953 (Box 491, Folder 2a-2b)
    - Winslow: wool, skins, pinons, shipments (received and sent), bills of lading (hides, pelts, furs). 1940-1950 (Box 491, Folder 3a-3b)
    - Location unknown: Indian accounts, accounts (team and kitchen), accounts (notations), "Inventory of C.D. Dedman's effects--April 15, 1915." 1909-1915 (Box 491, Folder 4)
    - Location unknown: Indian order, cash, "Mds Acct," credit account, daily sheet entries, "Kitchen Acct," various accounts. 1914-1915 (Box 491, Folder 5)
    - Location unknown: cash. 1922-1923 (Box 492, Folder 1a-1b)
    - Location unknown: various accounts, ledger sheets. 1936-1938 (Box 492, Folder 2)
    - Location unknown: various accounts. (Box 492, Folder 3)
    - Location unknown: Indian and various accounts. 1924 (Box 492, Folder 4)
    - Location unknown: cattle. (Box 492, Folder 5)
    - Location unknown: notes on materials and goods sent to Gallup Ceremonial and goods sold there. (Box 492, Folder 6)
    - Location unknown: daily sheets, monthly summaries. 1931-1941 (Box 492, Folder 7)
    - Location unknown: various post accounts, rugs. 1947-1948 (Volume 493)
  - Series II: Summary Records, 1882-1967
    Contains a wide range of materials concerned with a general accounting of the business on a monthly, quarterly, yearly basis (inventories, financial statements, profit and loss, accounts payable/receivable, etc.).
    - Big Mountain: inventories, statements, summaries, balance sheets, distribution, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1939-1950 (Box 494, Folder 1-5)
    - Black Mountain: inventories, statements, weekly and monthly sheets. 1914-1927 (Box 494, Folder 6-8)
    - Black Mountain: inventories and statements. 1931, 1933-1937 (Box 495, Folder 1-4)
    - Blue Canyon: statement of balance, recapitulation of business. 1927 (Box 495, Folder 5)
    - Canyon Diablo: inventories and statements. 1928-1932 (Box 495, Folder 6)
    - Cedar Springs: inventories, statements, summaries. 1911-1914 (Box 495, Folder 7)
    - Chinle: inventories and statements. 1915-1918 (Box 495, Folder 8)
    - Cornfields: inventories, statements, summaries. 1910-1915 (Box 495, Folder 9-10)
    - Cornfields: inventories, statements, summaries. 1916-1918 (Box 496, Folder 1)
    - Cow Springs: inventories, statements, monthly reports. 1935 (Box 496, Folder 2)
    - Dam Store: inventories. 1914-1915, 1917-1921 (Box 496, Folder 3)
    - Farmington Farm: statement of accounts. 1930-1931 (Box 496, Folder 4)
    - Frontier Trading Post: inventories, balances, statements, records of sales. 1944-1947 (Box 496, Folder 5)
    - Gallup: inventories, statements, cost/retail statements. 1914-1916, 1936, 1938, 1943 (Box 496, Folder 6)
    - Ganado: inventories, statements, accounts payable/receivable, monthly recapitulations, Indian accounts, miscellaneous records. 1889-1934 (Box 496, Folder 7-14)
    - Ganado: inventories, statements, cost/retail statements, financial and monthly statements, accounts receivable, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1935-1943 (Box 497, Folder 1-9)
    - Ganado: inventories, statements, balances, O.P.A. base date pricing charts, trial balances, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1944-1950 (Box 498, Folder 1-8)
    - Ganado: inventories, statements, balances, monthly summaries, profit and loss, state tax reports, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1951-1967 (Box 499, Folder 1-10)
    - Greasewood: inventories, statements, miscellaneous records. 1930-1936 (Box 500, Folder 1-5)
    - Hollywood: balance sheets, journal entries, statements. 1926-1928 (Box 500, Folder 6)
    - Hub Store: inventories, statements, cost/retail statements, monthly/daily sheets, miscellaneous records. 1933-1939 (Box 500, Folder 7-9)
    - Lorenzo Hubbell Motor Company: financial statements, audits, miscellaneous materials connected with individual car sales, sales contracts, automobile titles and registration, etc. 1924-1952 (Box 501, Folder 1-5)
    - Hubbell Service Station: inventories, accounts receivable, operating and financial statements. 1936-1939 (Box 501, Folder 6)
    - Keams Canyon: inventories, statements, monthly sheets. 1913, 1915-1917 (Box 501, Folder 7-9)
    - Long Beach: statements, sales. 1921-1922 (Box 501, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles: trial balance, inventory of assets, expenses. 1921-1922 (Box 501, Folder 11)
    - Marble Canyon: inventories, statements, distributions, profit and loss, charges and credits, monthly reports, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1929, 1938, 1945-1947 (Box 502, Folder 1-6)
    - Marble Canyon: inventories, statements, distributions, profit and loss, cash reports, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1948-1950 (Box 503, Folder 1-8)
    - Marble Canyon: inventories, gasoline pump readings, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1951-1952, 1955-1956, 1962 (Box 504, Folder 1-4)
    - Nakai Tso: inventories, statements, expenses, cost/retail statements. 1933-1937 (Box 504, Folder 5-8)
    - Nakai Tso: inventories, statements, distributions, cost/retail statements, monthly statements, recapitulations, balances, work sheets. 1938-1946 (Box 505, Folder 1-8)
    - Nakai Tso: inventories, accounts receivable, balances, monthly reports, work sheets. 1947-1950 (Box 506, Folder 1-6)
    - Nakai Tso: inventories, work sheets. 1951-1952 (Box 507, Folder 1-2)
    - Navajo Rug Shop, Phoenix: inventories, miscellaneous records. 1948, 1950 (Box 507, Folder 3)
    - Nazlini: inventories, monthly reports/statements. 1915-1918 (Box 507, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: inventories, statements, balances, accounts payable/receivable, loss and gain, financial statements, monthly sheets, miscellaneous records. 1914-1933 (Box 507, Folder 5-10)
    - Oraibi: inventories, statements, balance sheets, charges and credits, cost/retail statements, accounts payable/receivable, financial statements, Indian accounts, reports for taxes, miscellaneous records. 1934-1936 (Box 508, Folder 1-10)
    - Oraibi: inventories, statements, freight accounts, cost/retail statements, accounts payable/receivable, balance sheets, miscellaneous records. 1937-1938 (Box 509, Folder 1-7)
    - Oraibi: inventories, cost/retail statements, reports for taxation, assets and liabilities, accounts payable/receivable, balance sheets, freight accounts, financial statements, miscellaneous records. 1939-1940 (Box 510, Folder 1-7)
    - Oraibi: inventories, freight records, cost/retail statements, accounts payable/receivable, balances, estate appraisal, uncollectable accounts, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1941-1944 (Box 511, Folder 1-10)
    - Oraibi: inventories, statements, charges and credits, Indian accounts, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1945-1950 (Box 512, Folder 1-11)
    - Oraibi: inventories, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1951-1952 (Box 513, Folder 1-4)
    - Oraibi (probably): miscellaneous material. (Box 513, Folder 5-8)
    - Pinon: inventories, cost/retail statements, statements. 1918-1924, 1934-1935 (Box 513, Folder 9-11)
    - Pinon: inventories, statements, cost/retail statements, accounts receivable. 1936-1946 (Box 514, Folder 1-9)
    - Pinon: inventories, statements, bad debts, accounts receivable, accountability, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1947-1951 (Box 515, Folder 1-7)
    - Pinon: inventories, miscellaneous records. 1952 (Box 516, Folder 1)
    - The Pioneer: inventories, wholesale/retail statements, operating statements, accounts receivable, miscellaneous records. 1934-1938 (Box 516, Folder 2-6)
    - Sheep Springs: inventories, statements. 1914-1918 (Box 516, Folder 7)
    - Tenebito: inventories, statements, cost/retail statements, miscellaneous records. 1923-1924, 1931-1936 (Box 516, Folder 8)
    - Tenebito: inventories, statements, cost/retail statements, distributions, monthly reports, balances, charges and credits, Indian accounts, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1937-1948 (Box 517, Folder 1-9)
    - Winslow: inventories, balances, statements, accounts payable/receivable, trial balances, financial statements, freight accounts, payrolls, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1924-1926, 1928-1929 (Box 518, Folder 1-13)
    - Winslow: inventories, financial statements, accounts charged off, O.P.A. pricing, rationing points inventory, balances, audits, miscellaneous records, work sheets. 1944-1948 (Box 519, Folder 1-11)
    - Winslow: inventories, accounts payable/receivable, miscellaneous records, work sheets, annual audit, final statement of affairs. 1949-1953 (Box 520, Folder 1-7)
    - Winslow (probably): miscellaneous material. (Box 520, Folder 8)
    - Unknown locations (dated material). (Box 520, Folder 9)
    - Unknown locations. (Box 520, Folder 10)
    - Employee's wages records: miscellaneous accounts relating to Hubbell employees. (Box 521, Folder 1-3)
    - Traveling Salesmen's records: travel expenses, invoices of sale, etc( O.N. Gibson and others). (Box 521, Folder 4)
    - Traveling Salesmen's records: travel expenses, invoices of sale, etc (Thomas S. Hubbell). (Box 521, Folder 5)
    - Traveling Salesmen's records: travel expenses, invoices of sale, etc (Ernest V. Wesson). (Box 521, Folder 6)
    - Checks: lists of checks sent, checks needed, checks received, checks submitted by, checks issued for, etc. 1905, 1911, 1918, 1933-1935 (Box 521, Folder 7)
    - Checks: lists of checks sent, checks needed, checks received, checks submitted by, checks issued for, etc. 1936-1942 (Box 521, Folder 8)
    - Rugs/blankets: miscellaneous lists of baled or individual rugs for inventory, consignment, etc. (Box 521, Folder 9)
    - Pawn: various miscellaneous pawn lists mostly in the nature of inventories. (Box 522, Folder 1)
    - Pinons: miscellaneous records and lists. (Box 522, Folder 2)
    - Skins/pelts/hides: lists of credit or inventory purposes. (Box 522, Folder 3)
    - Stock (sheep and lambs, goats, cattle, horses, mules): sales, sales contracts, reservation buying permits and inspections, dipping records, stock destroyed because of Dourine, etc. 1900-1929 (Box 522, Folder 4)
    - Stock (sheep and lambs, goats, cattle, horses, mules): sales, sales contracts, reservation buying permits and inspections, dipping records, stock destroyed because of Dourine, etc. 1930-1939 (Box 522, Folder 5)
    - Stock (sheep and lambs, goats, cattle, horses, mules): sales, sales contracts, reservation buying permits and inspections, dipping records, stock destroyed because of Dourine, etc. 1940-1946 (Box 522, Folder 6)
    - Stock (sheep and lambs, goats, cattle, horses, mules): sales, sales contracts, reservation buying permits and inspections, dipping records, stock destroyed because of Dourine, etc. 1947-1949 (Box 522, Folder 7)
    - Stock (sheep and lambs, goats, cattle, horses, mules): sales, sales contracts, reservation buying permits and inspections, dipping records, stock destroyed because of Dourine, etc. 1950-1954 (Box 522, Folder 8)
    - Rationing, WWI and WWII: miscellaneous records, samples of rationing stamps, etc. (Box 523, Folder 1)
    - Wool: an assortment of records relating to the buying selling and shipping of wool, including contracts, lists of weights, etc. 1891, 1917-1939 (Box 523, Folder 2)
    - Wool: an assortment of records relating to the buying selling and shipping of wool, including contracts, lists of weights, etc. 1940-1949 (Box 523, Folder 3)
    - Wool: an assortment of records relating to the buying selling and shipping of wool, including contracts, lists of weights, etc. 1950s, 1960s (Box 523, Folder 4)
    - Mixed records: rugs, wool, pawn, skins, etc. (Box 523, Folder 5)
    - Inventories: Cedar Springs, Cornfields, Ganado. 1898-1910 (Box 523, Folder 6)
    - Inventories: Cedar Springs, Cornfields, Oraibi; Post office matter: list of mail sent to and from St. Michaels, Keams Canyon, Chinle, Cedar Springs. 1910-1911 (Box 523, Folder 7)
  - Series III: Indian Records, 1882-1967
    This is a miscellany and contains all the various kinds of records relating to Indians that could not consistently be located in previous series. Included here also are personal Indian materials.
    - Applications for [incentive] payments for shorn wool, unshorn lambs, Commodity Credit Corporation. 1955-1956, 1958-1962, 1964 (Box 524, Folder 1)
    - Purchases: ammunition applications (Charles Ilfeld Co.), farm machinery/equipment, Indian ram purchases, Navajo Tribe livestock fund. (Box 524, Folder 2)
    - Reimbursable agreements/receipts. 1916-1936 (Box 524, Folder 3)
    - Accounts with individual or families--various posts. 1907-1929 (Box 524, Folder 4)
    - Accounts with individual or families--various posts. 1930-1946 (Box 524, Folder 5)
    - Personal materials: schools/students (report cards, etc), accounting of deposits into interest accounts with Hubbells; miscellaneous personal items (veterans' training, railroad retirement board applications for benefits, appointments as judges of Indian courts, General Accounting Office settlements of claims, divorce notices, etc). (Box 524, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous loose materials relating to Emergency Conservation Work: roster of workers available and on work crews. (Box 525, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous loose materials relating to Emergency Conservation Work: rations issued or needed by workers/crews. (Box 525, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous loose materials relating to Emergency Conservation Work: material relative to payments to workers/crews. (Box 525, Folder 3-7)
    - Books containing various Emergency Conservation Work records. 1933 (Box 526, Folder 1)
    - Books containing various Emergency Conservation Work records. 1933-1934 (Box 526, Folder 2)
    - Books containing various Emergency Conservation Work records. 1933-1934 (Box 526, Folder 3)
    - Books containing various Emergency Conservation Work records. 1934 (Box 526, Folder 4)
    - Books containing various Emergency Conservation Work records. 1934-1936 (Box 526, Folder 5)
    - Reports, regulations, bulletins, etc. sent to trading posts by Indian agencies and by various other governmental agencies concerned with Indians and Indian trading posts. to 1939 (Box 527, Folder 1)
    - Reports, regulations, bulletins, etc. sent to trading posts by Indian agencies and by various other governmental agencies concerned with Indians and Indian trading posts. from 1940 (Box 527, Folder 2)
    - Materials relating to a proposed livestock loan company. (Box 527, Folder 3)
    - Navajo Trading by B. Youngblood: report and some materials related to it. (Box 527, Folder 4)
    - Payment chits to Indians for mechandise redemption at trading posts (located in the vault). 1900-1927 (Box 528)
- Sub-group IV: Legal Matters, 1884-1968
  - Maps, sections, printed/hand drawn, with notations; property lists. (Box 529, Folder 1)
  - Mortgages, deeds, titles, etc.: to land in Arizona: Apache, Navajo, and Pinal Counties. (Box 529, Folder 2)
  - Mortgages, deeds, titles, etc.: to land in New Mexico: Bernalillo, McKinley, San Juan, and Valencia Counties; to land in California and Kansas. (Box 529, Folder 3)
  - Leases: Arizona. Land Department: Aztec Land and Cattle Company; Santiago Baca; Bennett, Erb and Bennett, Los Angeles; New Mexico. Public Lands Department: New Mexico and Arizona Land Company; E.P. Parcher, Los Angeles; Billy Pete; Santa Fe Railway; J.F. Snively, Los Angeles. (Box 529, Folder 4)
  - Some materials relating to the clearing of the title of the Ganado land. (Box 529, Folder 5)
  - Trading posts: licenses, traders' bonds, materials relating to the acquiring or selling of posts: Big Mountain, Black Mountain, Blue Canyon, Canyon Diablo, Cornfields, Cow Springs, Dam Store, Ganado, Greasewood, Hub Store, Keams Canyon, Los Angeles, Marble Canyon, Nakai Tso. (Box 529, Folder 6)
  - Trading posts: licenses, traders' bonds, materials relating to the acquiring or selling of posts: Oraibi, Pinon, Pioneer Liquor Store, Tenebito, Winslow, all posts. (Box 529, Folder 7)
  - Estate of Lorenzo Hubbell, Jr.: various court records relating to the administration of the estate. (Box 529, Folder 8)
  - Estates: miscellaneous material relating to estates of Thomas S. Hubbell, Sr., and Thomas E. Thacker. (Box 529, Folder 9)
  - Henry Dodge V. Adele H. Parker, Barbara H. Goodman, Roman Hubbell, Lorenzo Hubbell, et al: various court records. (Box 529, Folder 10)
  - Affidavits: from various individuals concerning various subjects. (Box 529, Folder 11)
  - Bankruptcy notices (mostly) to creditors. (Box 529, Folder 12)
  - Chattel mortgages: J.L. Hubbell, Lorenzo Hubbell, Jr., Roman Hubbell, F.M. Parker, J.B. Stiles, C.A. and D.E. Wheeler. (Box 529, Folder 13)
  - Claims against estates. (Box 529, Folder 14)
  - Complaints and suits, some with summonses. (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - Contract for use of Farmington Farm by C.F.Carver. (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - Agreements for the feeding of sheep/cattle. (Box 530, Folder 3)
  - Notary's record of T.E. Thacker. April 13, 1909-September 13, 1923 (Box 530, Folder 4)
  - "Notice of Mining Location," the "Benado," Valencia County, New Mexico. (Box 530, Folder 5)
  - Powers of Attorney. (Box 530, Folder 6)
  - Protests of bad checks. (Box 530, Folder 7)
  - Stocks and bonds. (Box 530, Folder 8)
  - Subpoenas and summonses. (Box 530, Folder 9)
  - Writs of Garnishment and assignments of wages. (Box 530, Folder 10)
  - Taxation: general statement and lists, not related to specific properties. (Box 530, Folder 11)
- Sub-group V: Banking Matters, 1889-1966
  - The Albuquerque National Bank, with C.N. Cotton, Gallup. 1889-1890 (Box 531, Folder 1)
  - The Arizona National Bank, Tucson, with J.L. Hubbell. October 1914 (Box 531, Folder 2)